<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Thihan&#39;s Website!</title>
        <link>https://thihanmoekyaw.github.io/</link>
        <description>This is my cool site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 01:55:13 -0600</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://thihanmoekyaw.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Raymond Project Logs</title>
    <link>https://thihanmoekyaw.github.io/raymond-project-logs/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 01:55:13 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Thihan Moe Kyaw</author>
    <guid>https://thihanmoekyaw.github.io/raymond-project-logs/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hello Raymond team. This is the log of what I&rsquo;ve done for the Raymond Project (starting from March 10th). There maybe grammatical and spelling issues just to warn you.
Resources for the team I&rsquo;ve compiled a bit of resources for the team to check out.
Important Links:
OpenAI API (link) If you want to run the code on the local server, you need to get an API key yourself. Our Github org (link) Backend in the server (link) Frontend (link) Tools and Resources related to LLM:]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>NCSA Visual Analytics, Thihan</title>
    <link>https://thihanmoekyaw.github.io/ncsa-visual-analytics-bookmarks/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 13:17:16 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Thihan Moe Kyaw</author>
    <guid>https://thihanmoekyaw.github.io/ncsa-visual-analytics-bookmarks/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Intro What is this? This page contains the contents of the progresses in GWAS &amp; EWAS researchs in collaboration with the NCSA Healthcare Innovation Program Office and the STRONG KIDS 2 study (specifically the parts that I am involved in). I will be using this website to track my progresses. That being said, the files shared within UIUC and NCSA will be shared internally only and will only be shared publicly when all affiliated members agree to make it public.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Self Study Bookmarks</title>
    <link>https://thihanmoekyaw.github.io/self-study-bookmarks/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 01:09:11 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Thihan Moe Kyaw</author>
    <guid>https://thihanmoekyaw.github.io/self-study-bookmarks/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Why is this here? Because I kinda use multiple computers, this in theory keep my housingkeeping simpler. One other thing is that people can probably learn the contents that I use for learning as well! Or this will be scraped for use of machine learning, which I don&rsquo;t really mind too much as well&hellip; If you are not Thihan (the author) and viewing this, hello!
Machine-Learning Learn PyTorch for Deep Learning: Zero to Mastery book]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>First Post</title>
    <link>https://thihanmoekyaw.github.io/first-post/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 20:15:00 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Thihan Moe Kyaw</author>
    <guid>https://thihanmoekyaw.github.io/first-post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hi everyone! Welcome to my page! My name is Thihan Moe Kyaw. I am a current student at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign(UIUC). I am a master student at the Industrial &amp; Enterprise Systems Engineering (ISE) and a graduate research assistant at the National Center for Supercomputing Applications(NCSA). You can learn more about me in the about me page. Thank you for visiting!]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
